Contact

matthewysun2020@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ matthewyxsun2020 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
REST APIs
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
C++

Matthew Sun

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from UC Berkeley Rancho Palos Verdes, California, United States

Summary

I am a graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from UC Berkeley's College of Letters and Science. I've been enraptured by the inner workings of computer programs and the practical applications of these programs.

My focus is on software engineering, artificial intelligence and machine learning, and data processing and analysis. I have experience working with several general-purpose object-oriented programming languages like Java and C, and with Python for data manipulation, logic, algorithms, and AI.

Through my internships, I performed tests on semiconductor devices. I then collected, processed, cleaned, and analyzed the testing data that led to big real-world decisions and outcomes. With this experience, I became familiar with data analysis practices, data processing and cleaning, and data visualization techniques, particularly using MATLAB.

Experience

Efficient Power Conversion
Data Analyst Intern
June 2023 - August 2023 (3 months)
El Segundo, California, United States

Wrote MATLAB code to filter and process numerical simulation results data into human-readable results

Worked with simulation software (COMSOL) and organized collected data in Excel

Collaborated with experienced coworkers to collect and analyze graphical and numerical testing data

Presented final research analyses and conclusions to the Product Reliability Department and CEO/Management

Efficient Power Conversion Research And Development Intern June 2022 - August 2022 (3 months)

El Segundo, California, United States

Fast dR bench testing, high-voltage stress-testing, test data collection analysis, and test setup automation.

Semiconductor simulation in COMSOL Multiphysics, semiconductor modeling, resistance testing, simulation setup automation.

Education

University of California, Berkeley

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Computer Science · (August 2020 - May 2024)

Palos Verdes Peninsula High School High School Diploma, General Education · (August 2016 - June 2020)